<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Wildlife Conservation Physiology</title>
    <link>https://www.wildlifeconservationphysiology.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Wildlife Conservation Physiology</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-gb</language>
    
	<atom:link href="https://www.wildlifeconservationphysiology.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://www.wildlifeconservationphysiology.com/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.wildlifeconservationphysiology.com/about/</guid>
      <description>By improving our understanding of how free-living mammals function, the Wildlife Conservation Physiology team at the University of the Witwatersrand aims to contribute to informed conservation and management of arid-zone mammals.
We have two main research themes:
to understand the physiological plasticity available to free-living mammals to cope with climate change,
 to improve the physiological welfare of mammals during conservation management practices, such as immobilization and translocation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact</title>
      <link>https://www.wildlifeconservationphysiology.com/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.wildlifeconservationphysiology.com/contact/</guid>
      <description>Do you want to find out more about our work, collaborate with us, join us for PhD or MSc studies or as a postdoctoral fellow? Then please feel free to contact us using the form below.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Partners</title>
      <link>https://www.wildlifeconservationphysiology.com/partners/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.wildlifeconservationphysiology.com/partners/</guid>
      <description>Funding 
  
  
  
  
  
  
  
  
  
  
    Services     Collaborators Local  Graham Alexander, Marcus Byrne, Robyn Hetem and Francesca Parrini – University of the Witwatersrand, South Africa
 Nico Avenant – National Museum Bloemfontein, South Africa</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>People</title>
      <link>https://www.wildlifeconservationphysiology.com/people/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.wildlifeconservationphysiology.com/people/</guid>
      <description>Staff Andrea Fuller (PhD) andrea.fuller@wits.ac.za Andrea is director of the research group and a Professor in the School of Physiology at the University of the Witwatersrand, and an Extraordinary Lecturer in the Department of Paraclinical Sciences at the University of Pretoria.   Leith Meyer (BVSc, PhD) leith.meyerm@up.ac.za Leith is an Associate Professor in the Department of Paraclinical Sciences at the University of Pretoria, and an Honorary Senior Research Fellow in the School of Physiology at the University of the Witwatersrand.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Recent publications</title>
      <link>https://www.wildlifeconservationphysiology.com/publications/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.wildlifeconservationphysiology.com/publications/</guid>
      <description>2021  ANDERSON V, LEUNG AC, MEHDIPOOR H, JÄNICKE B, MILOŠEVIĆ D, OLIVEIRA A, MANAVVI S, KABANO P, DZYUBAN Y, AGUILAR R, AGAN PN, KUNDA JJ, GARCIA-CHAPETON G, FONSÊCA VDFC, NASCIMENTO ST, ZURITA-MILLA R. Technological opportunities for sensing of the health effects of weather and climate change: a state-of-the-art-review. International Journal of Biometeorology [online ahead of print], 2021. DOI:  https://link.springer.com/article/10.1007/s00484-020-02063-z
 BOYERS M, PARRINI F, OWEN-SMITH N, ERASMUS BFN, HETEM RS.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>